easywpseoplugin.com 2015-06-08

# Privacy Policy | Easy WP SEO Plugin

**What information is collected?**

EasyWPSEOPlugin.com collects information from you when you fill out a form, such as when you leave a comment.

When registering on this site, you may be asked to enter your name and e-mail address. You may, however, visit this site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..

**What is my information for?**

Any of the information collected from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience – your information helps me to better respond to your individual needs
  * To improve this website – I continually strive to improve my website offerings based on the information and feedback received from you
  * To improve customer service – your information helps me to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

**Does EasyWPSEOPlugin.com use cookies?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

EasyWPSEOPlugin.com uses cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements, and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that better site experiences and tools can be offered in the future.

Third parties may use cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies to collect or receive information from your website and elsewhere on the internet and use that information to provide measurement services and target ads. Visitors can opt out of Facebook ads via Facebook’s AdChoices link that appears with each advertisement.

**Is any information disclosed to outside parties?**

I do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. I may, however, release your information when I believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce this site’s policies, or protect my or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at my discretion, I may include or offer third party products or services on this website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. I therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, I seek to protect the integrity of this site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because I value your privacy I have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. I therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

EasyWPSEOPlugin.com is in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act). I do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Your Consent**

By using this site, you consent to this privacy policy.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

If I decide to change this privacy policy, I will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on 05/26/2011

**Questions?**

If you have any questions about my privacy policy, you may contact me at http://easywpseoplugin.com/contact/.
